*  
    
    Search
    
* Customer Support support@xcellme.com
    
    UAE +97143406288
    
    Bahrain +97317264277
    
    Kuwait +96522423852
    
    Oman +96824813939
    
    Qatar +97440296943
    
    Saudi Arabia +966559996553

* [0
    
    0 items 0.00 AED](https://www.xcellme.com/cart-2/)
* 

[X.Cell](https://www.xcellme.com/ "Go to X.Cell.") > The Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy
==================

Terms of Service

Disclaimer
----------

X.Cell is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the X.Cell Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the X.Cell Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

X.Cell website collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. X.Cell Website also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by X.Cell Website. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by X.Cell Website for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the X.Cell Website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through X.Cell Website public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: X.Cell Website does not read any of your private online communications.

X.Cell Website encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from X.Cell Website so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. X.Cell Website is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the X.Cell Website and X.Cell Website family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information
--------------------------------

X.Cell Website collects and uses your personal information to operate the X.Cell Website and deliver the services you have requested. X.Cell Website also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from X.Cell Website and its affiliates. X.Cell Website may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

X.Cell Website does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. X.Cell Website may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, X.Cell Website may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to X.Cell Website, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

X.Cell Website does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

X.Cell Website keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within X.Cell Website, in order to determine what X.Cell Website services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within X.Cell Website to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

X.Cell Website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on X.Cell Website or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of X.Cell Website; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of X.Cell Website, or the public.

Use of Cookies
--------------

The X.Cell Website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize X.Cell Website pages, or register with X.Cell Website site or services, a cookie helps X.Cell Website to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same X.Cell Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the X.Cell Website features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the X.Cell Website services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

X.Cell Website secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. X.Cell Website secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

X.Cell Website will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. X.Cell Website encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how X.Cell Website is protecting your information.

Contact Information
-------------------

X.Cell Website welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that X.Cell Website has not adhered to this Statement, please contact X.Cell Website at [support@xcellme.com](mailto:support@xcellme.com)

Upgrade your smart devices. Take your experience to the next level with the best in class accessories and top end devices.Our R&D makes sure each device/accessory is tested and molded to give you the best experience.

### Featured Products

    Rated **0** out of 5
    
    ~199.00 AED~ 99.00 AED
    
    Rated **0** out of 5
    
    199.00 AED
*  [ Clean Air CL1 Air Purifier by X.CELL, With Pre Filter, HEPA Filter, Activated Carbon Filter, UV Light And Ionizers, Protection from Pet hair, Pollen, Dust, Smoke, Dander, Cotton fibre, White](https://www.xcellme.com/product/clean-air-cl1/)
    
    Rated **0** out of 5
    
    ~699.00 AED~ 629.00 AED

### Top Rated Products

    Rated **5.00** out of 5
    
    ~229.00 AED~ 199.00 AED
    
    Rated **5.00** out of 5
    
    ~69.00 AED~ 49.00 AED
    
    Rated **5.00** out of 5
    
    99.00 AED

USEFUL LINKS
------------

### Newsletter

Leave this field empty if you're human: 

© 2023 - X.CELL

Menu

0

0 items 0.00 AED

Search

Customer Support support@xcellme.com

UAE +97143406288

Bahrain +97317264277

Kuwait +96522423852

Oman +96824813939

Qatar +97440296943

Saudi Arabia +966559996553

Search

Search

Recent Posts
------------

Recent Comments
---------------

1. Lester on [SOUL 10 Clear Sound, Rich Bass R…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-10-clear-sound-rich-bass-white/#comment-3290)
    
2. mahmoud on [Elite 4 Smart Watch Stainless Steel](https://www.xcellme.com/product/elite4-smartwatch-stainless-steel/#comment-3228)
    
3. Elon on [SOUL 12 PRO True Wireless Earbuds &…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-12-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-black/#comment-3067)
    
4. Alan dela cerna on [SOUL 10 PRO True Wireless Earbuds &…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-10-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-black/#comment-1924)
    
5. Anuhas on [SOUL 9 PRO True Wireless Earbuds Hi…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-9-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-high-bass-rich-sound-white/#comment-1624)

Search

Search

Latest Posts
------------

Latest Comments
---------------

1. Lester on [SOUL 10 Clear Sound, Rich Bass R…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-10-clear-sound-rich-bass-white/#comment-3290)
    
2. mahmoud on [Elite 4 Smart Watch Stainless Steel](https://www.xcellme.com/product/elite4-smartwatch-stainless-steel/#comment-3228)
    
3. Elon on [SOUL 12 PRO True Wireless Earbuds &…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-12-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-black/#comment-3067)
    
4. Alan dela cerna on [SOUL 10 PRO True Wireless Earbuds &…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-10-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-black/#comment-1924)
    
5. Anuhas on [SOUL 9 PRO True Wireless Earbuds Hi…](https://www.xcellme.com/product/soul-9-pro-true-wireless-earbuds-high-bass-rich-sound-white/#comment-1624)

Tags
----

There’s no content to show here yet.

Cart
----

[Home](https://www.xcellme.com/)[Account](https://www.xcellme.com/my-account-2/)[0

Cart](https://www.xcellme.com/cart-2/)[Categories](https://www.xcellme.com/categories/)

Welcome to our Online Shop. Please select your nearest Store.

Could not get your position

* * *

Not the store you searched for? We have more ...
